Here you go. It's starting.
Hallo! Stee, my partner this time is Eguchi Saya from BEYOOOOONDS / Chica Tetsu.
This is Honoka Kobayashi of BEYOOOOONDS / Seasonings.
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with me until the end.
Well, BEYOOOOONDS performed at the Nippon Budokan for the second time on May 15.
Thank you very much.
Actually, this Halo! I can't tell you how I feel about it now because the recording of this show was made before the concert, but I think that a lot of people came to the concert and it was a very exciting and enjoyable concert.
I think it was an exciting and enjoyable concert. I am sure that many people came to the concert and that it was a very exciting and enjoyable concert.
The Halo! Ste. will be distributed on May 17, which means that the rainy season is just around the corner, isn't it?
That's right.
Do you have any suggestions on how to enjoy rainy days?
I think it is a bit dark on rainy days, but I dare to enjoy the projector in the dark without turning on the lights in my room.
What do you have in mind? It is a way of spending rainy days. What do you have in mind? How to spend a rainy day.
I recently found a song about rain.
It doesn't have lyrics, but it has the sound of rain in it,
I found a song that I really like, and I enjoy the sound of the rain hitting the window while listening to it,
I'm looking forward to spending a rainy day with a good feeling.
It sounds wonderful.
Are there any songs in BEYOOOOONDS that are good to listen to on rainy days?
Yes, I do.
I have some songs from BEYOOOOONDS and Seasoning,
Get Back, The Great Adventure of the Plastic Umbrella,
There is a song called "Get Back" and "The Great Adventure of the Plastic Umbrella" that is perfect for the rain.
This song is about a plastic umbrella forgotten on a train,
Please listen to it once and you will never forget your umbrella on the train again,
Please give it a listen.
The BEYOOOOONDS concert tour NEOBEYO, which started in March, is now in its second half.
We will be visiting Yamaguchi Prefecture on the weekend of the 20th, so please come if you have a chance.
So, first of all, please take a look at this video.
Here you go! Mr. Ishida flies from A-Chome to My Phone 5Gm, and Mr. Sato rides his bicycle from B-Chome to My Phone 5Gm.
If they leave at the same time
How many minutes will it take for them to meet?
Put it all together.
It doesn't make sense.
When is it useful?
Well, not much, really.
But it never hurts to try.
What do we do?
Stand up, pull back, descend.
Get up, get out, get out. Come on, get out.
200 meters. Sheep and birds.
I'll break the distance.
25 minutes ago.
I'm a traveler of dreams.
I hold up my dreams and the miraculous second hand
the image of a shadow, bending over
The reason why we meet The perspective that leads us by the hand
Everyone is a traveler of destiny
Let's hope for life
Let's hope for a happy life Let's hope for a happy life Let's hope for a happy life Let's hope for a happy life Let's hope for a life
Even if it doesn't help me
I'm just standing here 'cause I'm having fun
♪ Life makes you want to laugh ♪
I can hope for more, more, more, more
Problem number two.
Mr. Kirai is running 200 meters per minute
He's running 200 meters per minute, three kilometers away.
That's terrible... even today... if you chase after him at 450 meters per minute...
How long would it take you to catch up to Mr. Hirai?
There's no end to the song, no matter how it comes true, it's still the same reality
It's a hard world to live in
But I won't give up on the easy way
What are you going to do?
Many, low, high...
Low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low, low.
2.5 million holes, that's normal.
Let's go with confidence, Junifanggo! Space High Governor Operated Airports
Junior Fanger!
You are a traveler of destiny
You've been waiting so long to catch up
Catching up with the longing
You're a boy and a girl
Your time is not wasted
Twist and turn
you saw me
A dream of blooming love
Kisei sa
Let's seek more and more and more and more
Pramai palapa
Palapar, I added it.
Pull, pull, pull.Subtracted. Subtracted.
It's a draw, it's a draw, it's a draw.
It's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over.
There are few absolutes in this world.
We're all here now, making mistakes.
We're all in the wrong place at the wrong time.
♪ Dream eye, dream eye, dream eye, dream eye ♪
Dream eye, dream eye, dream eye I'm walking alone
# Who am I crossing, where am I headed #
# I don't know where I'm going # I don't know where I'm going # It's game time to find the answer
Come on, let's run, run, run, run.
Everyone's a traveler on the sea
What do you want out of life?
What do I want from life What do I want from happiness
I'm happy even if I'm useless I'm happy even if I'm useless
Because I want you to laugh
I want what life has to offer
Pramai palapa
If I live tomorrow, if I live tomorrow, if I live tomorrow, if I live tomorrow, if I live tomorrow, if I live tomorrow, if I disappear, if I lose, if I disappear
If I disappear, if I lose, if I lose
Let's spend today slowly
Saya Eguchi of BEYOOOOONDS / Chica Tetsu and Honoka Kobayashi of BEYOOOOONDS / Seasonings bring you Halo! I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick pace.
Okay, let's go!
What items would you like to get for summer?
A necktie.
You graduated from music school in March. Has anything changed in your approach to music since you graduated?
The way I practice.
What skills does Honoka Kobayashi of BEYOOOOONDS want to acquire now?
Cooking skills
Honoka Kobayashi loves natto (fermented soybeans).
Natto dipped in miso, and miso dipped in sauce.
If you were to compare the current BEYOOOOONDS to a classical piece of music, what would it be?
New World
Oh, thank you very much!
Okay, now I'm going to dig into something I've been wondering about.
I'd like to dig a little deeper.
What has changed since you graduated?
How has your practice changed since you graduated?
Well, when I was going online, I was practicing for exams, practicing songs,
Recently, I've shifted to practicing songs and exercising my hands on the piano, and I've started a project to strengthen my muscles.
Wow, it looks like I'm going to further improve my piano skills.
And if you were to compare BEYOOOOONDS now to a classical piece, what would it be?
Yes, we are doing concerts in Neovio,
I chose to perform Dvorak's high school piece New World, just as the title says,
I chose it because I want to bring you a new world.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. No one can make it dirty, the night sky is watching over you.
BEYOOOOONDS new single, "In the night sky where you can't even draw a dream
Now on sale!
Boundless Moment Burn with all your life
It's me who makes me
Oh! Fever
Which one is loved?
Common sense says this way.
Tell me your tricks of the trade
You love me
You my life
You'll never be indebted to me
No matter how much I regret and how much I feel
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No more, no more, no more, no more, no more
Now on SAYO, now on SAYO, now on SAYO, now on SAYO, now on SAYO, now on SAYO, new album BIG LOVE
Now on SAYO
Halo! STE
Next, I would like to ask a question to Saya Eguchi.
Please give me your best regards.
Saya Eguchi likes to collect accessories. What is your latest favorite item?
Bracelet
As an idol with hashtag "legs that are too long," what do you usually take care of?
Massaging my feet.
It's been almost 5 years since you joined Chica Tetsu.
What is the first thing that comes to mind when you look back?
Performing on stage
What cosmetics have you bought recently?
Lip
Only 2 and a half months to go until I turn 20
What do you want to accomplish in your teenage years?
Cook my best dishes
Oh!
Yes, ma'am.Yes, sir.
It's been a few years since I joined Chica Tetsu.
The first thing that comes to mind when I look back
The stage
Yes, this is it.
Well, BEYOOOOONDS was formed and
and Seasonings joined us.
And soon after, there was the Alice stage, right?
At that time, there was a lot of compositions divided into units.
We performed those songs and had release events.
When I hear that you joined Chica Tetsu, the stage comes to mind.
What cosmetics have you bought recently?
This is a light pink lipstick with high moisturizing power.
I bought it from a sales clerk who recommended it as a primer and gloss, and I've been using it ever since.
I bought it and have been using it ever since. I'll continue after this.
I'm doing it. We'll continue after this.
This is Natsuyaki Masashi, and we're back with another member of Hello Kitchen, this time it's Ilia Lisa from Juice Juice, and this is her second Hello Kitchen appearance.
Hello teacher, what are you going to make this time?
Today we're going to make kawara soba.
Do you know it?
I've never heard of it.
When I heard we were making this, I looked it up.
That's great!
You did your research!
I also tasted the food after researching it.
I know some of you may not know the ingredients, so here are the ingredients.
Kawahara soba is a kind of local cuisine of Yamaguchi Prefecture,
When you eat it at a restaurant, the soba is served on top of the kawahara,
When you eat it at a restaurant, it is served with soba on top of the riverbank, but it is also eaten at home,
It is also eaten at home, and is served at home at least once or twice a month.
At that time, they cook it on a hot plate, so it is hot even at home.
So it's all right then.
Then I would like to start making it right away. Let's go for it!
First of all, I would like to make mycelial eggs.
I've only ever made eggs as thick as an omelette, but it's always difficult to transfer them to a plate after they're cooked.
I don't know, it's difficult.
It's a little tricky.
How do you like it?
Let's make it while you teach me the tricks.
Eggs... they crack.
That's good.
You can crack an egg.
Do you cook? What do you usually do, bully?
I cook a lot.
Yes, you do.
On my days off, I cook dinner for my family.
That's great.
Let's add a pinch of salt.
A little less than a tablespoon of sugar.
Yes, mix it all together.
It's like making sweets.
I'm looking forward to it.
There is this lump of white meat, so cut it as much as possible.
The yellowish yolk part mixes in pretty quickly, so make sure you get the white part well.
Once it's lost. It looks good.
Yes, I think it's good.
Turn it well.
The heat is the most difficult thing to control with eggs, to be honest.
It's very difficult. The condition of the frying pan is also important, so if it is too hot, the eggs will be overcooked.
You can start out with a high heat, but it should be a little lower than medium or medium-high heat. All over. Yes, I did.
Start from the center,
All over with the left hand.
Slices.
Does it look okay to you? It's not stuck?
Maybe not enough?
Let's put it in.
And put it down. It's okay.
It looks good.
Now we wait.
Next, right? Next, we're going to turn it over.
I think it's ready.
I think it's ready... but the day before there were a few... it's hard to do...
I'll help you.
I'll help you spread them out.
Perfectly done!
I think it's perfect, isn't it?
I'm sure there are many ways to do it, but I don't want it to be too thin because it tends to get tangled up with the wheat.
You are very experienced. You are a regular cook.
You can use this egg in many ways, so you should make it on a regular basis.
It can be used for hand-rolled sushi, shirashi sushi, and so on.Or even hand-rolled sushi, or shirashi sushi.
Just put this kind of thing on the place where you eat rice.
You did a really good job cutting it.
It looks great!
Now let's move on to the next one.
Let's continue.
I'd like to grill some meat to put on top of the soba noodles.
It's a cut of wagyu beef.
Wow, that looks delicious!
It looks delicious! It's quite a lot of meat! Thank you very much!
For example, the size of the meat is like this.
For example, if the size of the meat is this big, it will be this big when it is cooked.
If there is a long part, please cut it off.
Please take a look! I'm trying to do it in layers!
It's perfect!
But don't worry about the small ones.
Just find the long ones.
About 3 equal pieces will be fine.
I love meat.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm glad.
Let's fry it.
We'll cook it in the end.
It's more like...
I'd like to brown the surface a little bit.
I'd like to brown the surface a little to bring out the aroma.
It's okay if it doesn't brown completely over medium heat.
If the side you put it on gets some color, I think it's okay to take it off.
It's grilled meat, it's completely grilled meat.
The first one I put on the grill, it's changing color, so be careful.
If you think it's getting hotter, you can stop it.
Yes, with residual heat.
Okay, it's ready.
Here's the point of Miyahi vinegar.
Dissolve the flavor of grilled meat with mirin.
So, how does this look like, sir?
There's a lot of oil.
I'll wipe off the oil.
Just the oil.
Leave the umami here.
Leave the flavor here? It's hard! This is hard!
You mean the kind that leaves a brownish residue when you wipe it off?
Yes! That's right.
I want to keep the brown here.
Not wine.
Mirin.
Baked with mirin.
You want to try this?
Wow. Wow.
You want to give it a shot?
If you put some in first.
Sure.
It's already pretty hot.
Fire it up.
Don't go nuts. Not yet.
Take it easy.
Put some liquid on it.
Okay, oh, it's not coming on.
Oh, it's not sticking.
Oh, you're pushing it pretty hard.
I don't know if it's gonna hold today.
Oh, it's not gonna hold.
That's too bad.
I noticed.
But you were doing a pretty good job with the momentum.
You're flying already.
It's flying.
I'm fine.
It's just a little bit...
It's a little thicker.
And the color.
Here, 2 tablespoons of soy sauce... to make it thicken, and then the color.
Here, 2 tablespoons soy sauce.
1 tablespoon sugar.
Add 100 cc of water.
I hope it's good.
It smells good.
It's got a lot of flavor.
Let's put it in.Let's put it in.
Keep it as close to the bottom as possible so it doesn't bounce, and this is important.
This is the important part.
This is all the umami.
Don't let it run off.
How can I put it all in?
Clean it up.
If you can't get it out...
Just put a little water here.
I see... you've already poured it in.
Umami is very important.
If I didn't know that... Umami is so important.
If I didn't know that, I'd wash it.
No, no, no, no, absolutely not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to turn off the heat and transfer it here.
Just the meat.
The juices are in the juices.
Separate.
We'll put in soba noodles at the end.
It's browned nicely, isn't it?
I'll put this on top.
You're a pain in the ass, sir.
Only this part is messy.
It's too fine.
Fine?
It's important.
Today is important.
Let's do it right.
Yes, perfect.
That's all for this time.
Next time, we'll finally finish it!
Please look forward to it.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
A little more firmly down there.
Wow!
Nice sound!
Wow, that's great, isn't it?
I can't wait to see the finished product.
How is the cooking situation?
I don't usually cook for myself.
Lately liner
I make shortcakes in winter.
If you have a recipe, you can do it.
Yes, that's right. I can make it without doing too much work,
I would like to try cooking something again.
Yes, I would like to try cooking again.
Studio Staff
Staff Staff Staff Staff Staff Staff
Staff version Staff version Staff version Staff version
Today, our trainees will show the results of their daily lessons in their solo performances. This diagnostic test is often the catalyst for their debut.
Now, let's move on to the second half of the show, where we'll be doing all the production work, costumes, etc.
The second half will be a free song block, where the students will be responsible for all aspects of the performance, including the production and costumes.
Brand new Blue Jean!
I put on shoes without thinking, I held up a big dream, and I became beautiful.
A brand-new youth, dressed up in a stylish way
Like a sweet and sour movie
Take me love all the time
Even though I'm a toddler, I'm a toddler
Love me, love me, love me, love me
I want to fuck you up so bad
Love me too
Love me, love me, love me, love me, love me
Love me, love me, love me, love me
I want it so bad
Love me too
You ask me what I want
But if I tell you, you'll be surprised
When I start talking about things you don't know
But when I start to tell you something you don't know
We're still in the middle of our dreams
We're all still dreaming.
That's enough.
Don't be like that.
The opportunity is out there.
Yeah!
Sad heaven, my heart is thirsty
Just one dream is enough for me
Seventh Heaven Someday I'll get there, I'll get lost in this endless sky
Dazzling Adult Eve
It's only a man and a womanIt is only men and women
It's better to embrace boldly
It all makes sense.
You and I, we can't live apart after all
The only answer I can think of is to hold each other
Because we embrace each other, we can live
Let's dance HAPPY TOWN
I'm happy town, I'm happy town
I can hear your heartbeat
More and more HAPPY SONG
This is the HAPPY SONG
This is it
Gently again
Upset field is
Pappa Pappa Pappa Pappa Pappa Pappa
I want to do a menchi-deppa-da-sou
Pappa Pappa Pappa
I want to love you so much, memory mike
But don't stop, don't stop, don't stop
Happy song
With you, with your friends, with your dreams, with your sweat
Someday there won't be a time of constant freedom
And all the bad things will blow away
A time that won't make you sad
Kampai baby, paper cups won't hurt you
Oh, yes, it's the thought that counts
Decorations are just for baubles and baubles
Oh yes, ideas Show
Tell me Tell me, my love
When you're lonely, baby, baby, baby
Tell me Tell me Tell me
It's true that it's a little bit nice
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Choo-choo-choo, it's so good
Lukewarm wind
Wrapping me up in it
Your whistling
Darling, I don't want to get separated from you
Please, please, keep going through the drizzling rain
Tututuru tu
Someday we'll walk side by side, look, to the one the sound calls, the audience applauds,
However, due to the overwhelming number of votes received by the two artists, we have decided to award two prizes this year.
The two awards are the Semi-Best Performance Award and the Best Performance Award.
First of all, the Semi-Best Performance Award goes to Risa Ogata.
The Semi-Best Performance Award goes to,
Hana Goto.
Congratulations.
Congratulations. The best.
Now, Ms. Ozawa. How do you feel about the Semi-Best Performance Award?
I hope I have become an idol among you all today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much. And lastly. I would like to announce the Best Performance Award.
Mr. Miyamoto, please.
The Best Performance Award goes to,
Miki Kawashima.
Congratulations.
Now, Ms. Kawashima, please go to the center of the room.
Yes, I am. Congratulations.
Ms. Kawashima.
Please tell us what you think.
Yes, I did. Well..,
You did it.
I was very happy to win the Best Performance Award this time.
If I put in the effort,
My goal for this performance was to show you a new me,
My goal for this performance was to show you a new me, and I am very honored that I was able to do that.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thanks to your enthusiastic support, I believe the trainees were able to show their abilities.
Thank you all for your continued support of the Halo Pro trainees.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your support today.
Thank you very much. Iris has found her idol. Iris has found her idol. Iris found her idol.
Iris found Iris's idol.
Iris found Iris's idol
Iris found Iris's idol.Iris has found her idol.
Iris has found her idol in Iris. I'm rooting for you in every moment! Keep up the good work!
Next is the presentation of lyrics that touched my heart!
Project has many wonderful lyrics, but
Project, but the song that I listen to when I want to work hard the most is the one by Juice-Juice.
Juice-Juice's "Zenkotsu Kake Go"!
I always listen to this song when I stop or when I want to do my best.
I, Kobayashi, am appearing in the VTR, so please take a look at it.
Please take a look.
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of Hello! Project songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Wataru Kobayashi, will be presenting a song.
So, here it is. I know me better than anyone else, so I have to believe in you more than anyone else.
I miss you. This is a song by Morning Musume。
We sang this song together as the last song at the Kacho Fugetsu concert,
From the beginning of the solo part, I was standing in a pose,
My team was the first to sing with Ms. FUKUMURA,
My team started with Ms. Fukumura's warm voice, and I stood there listening to the lyrics the whole time.
Gradually, more and more songs were assigned, and we were all singing the lyrics together,
When I was singing the lyrics, I was with myself more than anyone else, thinking about myself,
I chose this lyric because it was a moment when I felt I had to believe in myself, even if I was scared or something.
It was a really good song.
I was most impressed by it in iWISH.
I think so too.
This song is supposed to be kind, bright, and happy,
I really like the way it makes you feel a bit lonely,
It's not like everyone else is there, but rather, it's about taking care of yourself,
I think it is a wonderful song because it is about taking care of people,
The lyrics are also wonderful.
I think the lyrics are very beautiful.
You might be wearing earphones or something,
I think these lyrics are very touching when you are alone,
I think it is a good song to listen to alone.
Please look forward to the next installment!
Hello! Sta.
BEYOOOOONDS / Chica Tetsu Exegetes.
BEYOOOOONDS / Seasonings' Honoka Kobayashi presents Halo! Ste.
It is time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
The BEYOOOOONDS concert tour NEOBEYO is now underway.
This weekend, May 20, it will be held at Yamaguchi Park.
It's called NEOBEYO, which means singing, dancing, and playing instruments,
It's really BEYOOOOONDS, NEO,
I hope to bring you all something new and exciting.
Please enjoy it.
And our 4th single "Seek yo Fate no Tabibito Yoru Kukanai Yume no Dakunai Yozora ni" is now on sale!
It is a really wonderful song, and I hope you will listen to it as much as possible.
The music video is also really wonderful and overflowing with love, so please watch it a lot!
The music video is also full of love, so please watch it as much as you can. Project members will appear on the channel every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Saya Eguchi from BEYOOOOONDS Chica Tetsu and Sayu Kobayashi from BEYOOOOONDS / Seasonings.
This time we have Saya Eguchi from BEYOOOOONDS / Chica Tetsu and Honoka Kobayashi from BEYOOOOONDS / Seasonings ,Good bye